Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.twelve Mss.B.B61.inventory12
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents S
  - Schuman, Frederick L. (Box 80)
    - See FB open letter, Spain, Replies, 1938 Jan.
  - Schurman, Jacob Gould (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 22
  - Schurz, Carl (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1886 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1903 Aug. 12
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 7
    - From Boas, 1904 May 10
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov. 29
    - From Boas, 1905 May 8
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 1
      - see FB To White, Andrew, 1905 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1904 May 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1904 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 8
    - See McAneny, G., 1929 Feb. 25
      re: CS Memorial
  - Schurz, Carl L. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1906 May 18
    - See Butler, Nich. M., 1908 Nov. 10
    - From Boas, 1919 May 20
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 1
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 6
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 7
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 29
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 13
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 13
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1906 May 25
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1920 May 5
    - To Boas, 1920 May 8
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 8
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, n.y. Oct. 24; 1p
    - From Columbia Univ. Lib., 1920 Oct. 7
    - From Columbia Univ. Lib., 1920 Nov. 17
    - To Germanistic Soc. of Am. Relief, German Children, 1920 Feb.; 2p
      Also see Hepburn A. B. Metz, Herman A. Speyer, James
  - Schurz, Wm. L. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 12
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 20; 2p
  - Schuster, Rose (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 16
  - Schutz [?], Agatha (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 9; 3p
  - Schutz, H. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 14
  - Schütz, L.H. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 4; 2p
  - Schuyler, Montgomery (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 5
    - To Boas, 1903 May 12
  - Schwab, George (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 18
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 21; 2p
  - Schwab, Gustav H. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1904 May 3
      - co-signers: Choate, J., 1906 May 26
      - Smith, C.S.
      - Cillis, H.
      - Shepard, C.M.
      - Straus, O.S.
      - McAneny, G.
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 11; 4p
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 14
  - Schwab, Mrs. Hermann C. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 28
  - Schwab, J.C. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 15
  - Schwab Printing Co. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 15
  - Schwabacher, W.S. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 23
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 24
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1934 May 1
    - From Boas, 1934 May 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1934 May 22
    - From Boas, 1934 May 23
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1934 May 2
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 25
  - Schwabisch, Max (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1939 May 12
      Schwaebischer-Schiller Verein follows Schwarz, M.
  - Schwaebischer Schiller-Verein (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 5
      money order receipt dues card
  - Schwalbe, G. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1895 Feb. 3; 4p
    - To Boas, 1895 Mar. 31; 4p
    - To Boas, 1895 Apr. 25; 3p
    - To Boas, 1895 May 27; 3p
    - To Boas, 1895 July 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 29
  - Schwalbe, J. (Box 80)
    - To Einhorn (enc. 2/13/23 Danziger, Ernst to Heuser, F.W.), 1923 Jan. 17; 4p
  - Schwartz, Benjamin (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 9
  - Schwartzman, Ephraim (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 23
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 20
  - Schwarz (Box 80)
    - From Boas (see FB to Rappopart), 1909 May 6
  - Schwarz, D.J. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1939 May 20
  - Schwarz, Mrs. Else (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 4
  - Schwarz, Ernst (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 14
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 18; 2p
  - Schwarz, Herman (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 15
    - To Erstein, B., 1919 Aug. 25
  - Schwarz, Leo W. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 1
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1936 June 22
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1937 May 7
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 4
  - Schwarz, Marguerite (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 4
  - Schwarz, Osias (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 25
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 28
    - From Boas, 1909 June 5
    - From Boas, 1909 June 21
    - From Boas, 1909 July 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1909 July 8
    - To Boas, 1909 July 12
    - To Boas, 1909 July 16
    - To Boas, 1909 July 22
    - To Boas, 1909 July 29
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 2
    - To Boas, 1910 Sep. 12
    - From Crane, M.E., 1910 Dec. 31
  - Schwatka, Frederik (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1885 Sep. 16
  - Schwatt, J.J. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 19
  - Schweinitz, D. v. (Box 80)
    - Notgemeinschaft der Deut. Wissenschaft, Berlin
    - To Boas, 1923 July 12
    - To Boas, 1923 July 26
  - Schweitzer, Rose M. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1937 June 19
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 14
  - Schweizerbart, E. -- Verlagsbuchhandlung (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 23
  - Schwellenbach, L.B. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 23
  - Schwidetus [?] (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1935 May 3
  - Schwitalla (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1934 July 16
  - Science (Box 80)
    - From Business Mgr., 1895 Dec. 6
    - From Boas to Editor, 1902 Nov. 8; 6p
    - See FB Statement, 1939 Dec. 31
      See Cattell, J. McK.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 2
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 20
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 28
  - Science Service (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1937 July 20
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 16
      (notes attached by FB)
    - See Thone, Frank, 1936 May 1
    - To Boas, 1936 May 11
    - To Boas, 1936 May 28
    - To Boas, 1936 June 11
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 7
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 14
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 15
    - See Bender, M.G., 1936 May 12
  - Scientific Exploring Association (Box 80)
    - See Koshkin, F.B., 1933 Jan. 20
  - Scientific Institute for Research of the Biology of Jews (Box 80)
    - Enc. with Weidenreich, F., 1934 May 12
  - Scott & Van Altins (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct. 22
  - Scott, B.N. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1938 June 9
  - Scott, Emmett J. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 20
    - EJS -- to Locke, A.L., 1925 Dec. 10
  - Scott, E. McK. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 26
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 19
  - Scott, Frank W.- -- D.C. Heath & Co. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 16
    - From Boas, 1928 May 29
    - From Boas, 1928 June 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 July 5
    - From Boas, 1928 July 17
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 14
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 11
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 30
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1928 June 1
    - To Boas, 1928 June 15
    - To Boas, 1928 June 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 July 11
    - To Boas, 1928 July 13
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 14
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 8
  - Scott, H.L. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 28
  - Scott, James Brown (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 26
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 28
  - Scott, J.J. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 3
  - Scott, W.A. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 8; 2p
  - Scott, Walter D. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 3
    - See Baker, Frank E., 1939 Dec. 31
  - Scott, Z.E., Asst. Com. of Education (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 17
  - Scribner's, Charles Sons (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1888 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1888 Feb. 6 and Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1888 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1888 Feb. 9
  - Seabury, Samuel (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 31
  - Seamans, H.L. (Box 80)
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 22
  - Searle, Robert W. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 17
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 25
  - Searles, Stanley (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 24
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 6
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 18
    - From Boas, 1927 June 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 25
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 24
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1919 Sep. 9
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 27
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 30
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 4
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1927 June 24
    - From Gill, D., 1927 June 16
  - Seashore, C.E. (Box 80)
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 23
    - From Boas, 1928 May 3
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 7
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 14
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 31
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 6
    - From Boas, 1931 May 19
    - From Boas, 1935 May 14
    - From Boas, 1935 May 27
    - From Boas, 1935 June 28
    - From Boas, 1935 July 11; 3p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 11
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 9
    - To Boas, 1928 May 5
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 17
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1931 May 12
    - To Boas, 1931 May 22
    - (CES' sec'y, D. Regur), 1936 Jan. 13
    - See FB to Woodworth, R., 1931 Sep. 2
  - Seaver, Jay W. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1893 Dec. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1893 Dec. 31; 2p
  - Sechehaye, A. (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 15
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 6
    - From Boas, 1931 June 29
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 6
    - To Boas, 1931 July 24
    - Sechehaye -- from Schrijnen, J., 1930 Feb. 18
  - Seckendorf, M. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 22
  - Secretaria de Educasion Publica (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1922 July 12
    - To Boas, 1922 Aug. 24
  - Secretary (Box 81)
    - 1926 Dec. 17, 2p
  - Sedat, William (Box 81)
    - To Sapir, E., 1937 June 22; 2p
  - Sedgwick, Ellery (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 26
  - Sedgwick, W.T. (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1910 July 27
    - To Boas, 1910 July 17
  - Seeliger, H. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1922 Feb. 20
      - co-signer:
        - Müller, Karl Alex. v.
          enc. paper on nutrition by Rudolph Martin & Max Rubner
  - Seelman, Ernest P. (Box 81)
    - See FB to Lombardo, C.J., 1940 Oct. 14
  - Seelmann, Theodore (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1936 June 27
  - Seerey, Chief Inspector Police Department (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 8
  - Segall, S.O. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 14
  - Seher, August (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 6
  - Seher, Louise P. [Mrs. August] (Box 81)
    - To Boas with enc., 1920 Oct. 4; 2p
  - Seidenadel, Carl Wilhelm (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1908 May 1
    - Igorot grammar, etc., 1908 Mar. 16; 3pand
    - To Boas, 1908 June 13
  - Seilern, Oswald (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 14
    - From Boas, 1932 June 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 20
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 19
  - Selbach, F.W. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1908 June 13
  - Seldes, Gilbert (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 20
  - Seler, Eduard - Mus. f. Volkerkunde, Berlin (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1903 Sep. 23
    - From Boas, 1905 May 29
    - From Boas, 1905 Sep. 20
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 17
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 19
    - From Boas, 1906 May 12
    - From Boas, 1906 July 12
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 7
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 19; 3p
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 May 28
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 28; 4p
    - also see FB to Gordon, G, 1910 Nov. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 18
    - also see FB to Butler, N, 1910 Nov. 26
    - also see FB to Dixon, RB, 1911 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Jan. 25; 2p
      - also see FB to ChC!vez, E., 1911 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1911 Mar. 27; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 May 11
    - From Boas, 1911 May 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 May 13
    - From Boas, 1911 June 8
    - From Boas, 1911 June 12
    - From Boas, 1911 Dec. 31; 2p
    - From Boas, 1912 Sep. 8
    - From Boas, 1912 Sep. 10
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 23
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 27
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 4
      - also to Gordon, GB, 1913 Feb. 21
      - ChC!vez, E.K.
      - Butler, N.M., 1913 Mar. 3; 3p
    - From Boas, 1913 June 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Aug. 7
    - From Boas, 1913 Aug. 31; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 July 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 1
      - see FB to ChC!vez, E., 1913 Aug. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 24; 3p
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 15
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb 17
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb 20
    - From Boas, 1914 May 14, May 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 May 27
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 23
      - and to Butler, Gordon, 1914 Oct. 26
      - and to Butler, Gordon, 1914 Oct. 29
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 30
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 4; 4p
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1916 Jan. 28; 8p
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 9
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 21; 3p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 17
    - To Boas, 1888 Oct. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1889 Feb. 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1892 Aug. 23
    - To Boas, 1892 Dec. 5; 3p
    - To Boas, 1893 July 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1894 July 26
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1894 Oct. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1895 May 6
    - To Boas, 1898 Sep. 8
    - To Boas, 1900 Jan. 22; 5p
    - To Boas, 1903 Jan. 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1903 May 20
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 7; 3p
    - To Boas, 1904 Apr. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Sep. 9; 4p
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 13; 4p
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 28 and Sep. 18
    - To Boas, 1907 June 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 14 and Oct. 10; 4p
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 18 and Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 16; 4p
      - (translation), 1908 Nov. 16; 3p
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 18
    - To Boas, 1908 June 4
    - To Boas, 1909 June 12; 4p
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 1; 4p
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 11
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 30; 3p
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1911 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1911 July 11
    - To Boas, 1911 July 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 July 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 July 26
    - To Boas, 1911 Aug. 7
    - To Boas, 1911 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1911 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1912 July 16
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 23
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 June 20
    - Interna. School Amer. Archae., 1913 July 30
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 24
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 14; 4p
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1914 May 27
    - To Boas, 1915 June 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 May; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 12
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1920 May 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1922 Feb. 3
    - To Boas, 1922 Mar. 11; 2p
      - see Ford, J.B., 1924 June 24
    - From Andrews, H.A., 1908 June 30
    - To von Trottza Solz, 1913 July 24; 4p
  - Seler-Sachs, Celia (Mrs. Eduard) (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1911 Apr. 28; 3p
    - From Boas, 1924 June 5
    - From Boas, 1924 July 3
    - From Boas, 1924 June 14
    - To Boas, 1911 June 19
    - To Boas, 1911 July 3
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 12
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 12
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 16; 6p
    - To Boas, 1924 June 19
    - To Boas, 1924 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1924 Sep. 10
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 July 2
    - To Boas, 1930 June 27
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 14; 2p
    - From Ehrenreich, G., 1924 Sep. 10
  - Selig, Anna & Geisler, Friedrich -- to Boas, III/20/27 (Box 81)
  - Seligman, C.G. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 23
  - Seligman, Erwin R.A. (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 4
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1912 Aug. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 9
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 14; 4p
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 14; 4p
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 16; 4p
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 24; 6p
    - From Boas, 1917 May 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 May 22; 3p
    - From Boas, 1917 May 23; 3p
    - From Boas, 1917 June 5
    - From Boas, 1917 June 12
    - From Boas, 1917 June 13
    - From Boas, 1917 June 23; 7p
    - From Boas, 1917 July 25
    - From Boas, 1917 July 30
    - From Boas, 1917 Sep. 6
    - From Boas, 1917 Sep. 13
    - From Boas, 1917 Sep. 22
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 14
    - From Boas, 1918 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1918 June 6
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 31
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 12
    - From Boas, 1933 July 5
    - From Boas, 1934 May 1
    - From Boas, 1934 May 9
    - From Boas, 1934 July 30
    - From Boas, 1935 May 20
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 1
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 25
    - To Boas, 1916 Jan. 7
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 12
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 May 8; 6p
    - To Boas, 1917 June 7 and June 14
    - To Boas, 1917 July 2
    - To Boas, 1917 July 7
    - To Boas, 1917 July 27
    - To Boas, 1917 Sep. 10
    - To Boas, 1917 Sep. 17
    - To Boas, 1918 June 20
    - To Boas, 1923 May 6
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 31
      enc. letters to ERS from Wissler, C, Angell, J.R., Mitchell, W.C., Taussig, F.W Cardoza, B.N., Young, A.A., Ogburn, W.F. Frankfurter, F.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 11
      - Encyclo. Soc. Sci., 1930 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1931 May 2
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 14
      - enc. ERS to Murrow, 1935 June 5
    - To Cattell, J. McK., 1917 June 14; 2p
    - To Cattell, J. McK., 1917 June 18; 2p
    - To Murrow, E.R., 1935 June 5
    - To Osborn, H.F., 1917 June 4
    - To Hallowell, A.I., 1927 Oct. 20; 2p
    - To Hrdlicka, A., 1926 Apr. 26
    - From Angell. J.R., 1926 Mar. 2
    - From Butler, N.M., 1917 May 12
    - From Cardozo, B.N., 1926 Mar. 8
    - From Cattell, J.M., 1917 Mar. 8
    - From Cattell, J.M., 1917 June 13; 2p
    - From Cattell, J.M., 1917 June 14; 2p
    - From Cattell, J.M., 1917 June 16
    - From Cattell, J.M., 1917 June 16
    - From Cattell, J.M., 1917 June 23
    - From Frankfurter, F., 1926 Mar. 8
    - From Hrdlicka, A., 1926 Apr. 17
    - From Merriam, C.E., 1926 Mar. 3
    - From Mitchell, W.C., 1926 Mar. 11
    - From Ogburn, W.F., 1926 Mar. 9
    - From Taussig, F.W., 1926 Mar. 17
    - From Weinberger, H., 1927 Mar. 18
    - From Wissler, C., 1926 Mar. 17
    - From Young, A.A., 1926 Mar. 8
  - Seligman, Eustace (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1942 May 7
  - Seligman, Isaac N. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 25; 2p
  - Seligmann, Hans (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1929 July 25; 2p
  - Seligmann, H.J. (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1938 May 23
    - From Boas, 1938 June 9
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 21
    - From Boas, 1939 May 3
    - From Boas, 1939 July 8
    - To Boas, 1938 May 18
    - To Boas, 1938 May 21
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 30
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 9
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 20 andApr. 5 andJune 20 andJuly 7andJuly 14; (2p)
      - re Nazi encyclopedia, 1939 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1940 July 24
  - Seligmann, Kurt (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1940 July 1; 2p
  - Selle, W.A. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 7
      see also Univ. of Sydney. Registrar.
  - Selmer-Anderssen, O. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 8
  - Seltzer, A. (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 18
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 15
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 13
  - Selwyn, R.C. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1894 July 19
  - Semkhovitch, O. -- [or U or V.] (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 26; 2p
  - Semmes, P.R. (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1915 July 9
    - To Boas, 1915 July 27
  - Semmons, E.M. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 31
  - Semon, Kurt M. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 14
  - Senator, David W. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 23
  - Senators of N.J. (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1919 May 19; 5p
      - enc. FB to Mussey, H.R., 1919 May 20
  - Sender, Mrs. Toni (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 16; 2p
  - Senner [Sennex?], A. van (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1926 June 9; 2p
  - Seoguch, W.T. (Box 81)
    - 1910 Aug. 11
  - Sergi, G. (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 14
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1902 Aug. 2
    - To Boas, 1923 Aug. 8
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 14
    - To Boas, 1933 July 5
  - Sering, M. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 2; 3p
  - Serra y Pagér, R. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 1; 2p
  - Servants of India Soc. (Box 81)
    - see Rao, K.P., 1936 Jan. 12
  - Seton [?], S.A. (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1914 Apr. 16
  - Setzler, Frank M. (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 1
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 1
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 24
      - list enc., 1937 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 6
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 13
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 24
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 5
    - To Reichard, G.A., 1937 Feb. 4
  - Seymour, Charles (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 7
  - Seymour, Thomas Day (Box 81)
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Nov.19
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 13
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 24
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 8
    - From Boas, 1907 May 6
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1904 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 30
    - To Boas, 1907 May 4
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 24
  - Seytter, Emil (Box 81)
    - To Boas, 1896 Feb. 14
    - To Boas, 1896 May 4
    - To Boas, 1896 June 16
    - To Boas, 1896 July 22
    - To Boas, 1896 Aug. 3
    - To Boas, 1896 Aug. 23
    - To Boas, 1896 Dec. 8
  - Shafer, Robert (Box 82)
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 26
      - attached to RS of July 24, 1930 July 29
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 24
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 6
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov. 24
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 21